screensavers.com 2009-10-12

# Privacy Policy - Screensavers.com

## SCREENSAVERS.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to the Screensavers.com website. We understand that your trust depends on how we respect your privacy and how we safeguard information you provide us. We want you to feel comfortable using our website, products and services and encourage you to read this Privacy Policy, detailing the online practices for Screensavers.com ("Screensavers"). 

## Screensavers' Offers 

On Screensavers.com, you can download software and content, order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion such as by commenting on or reviewing a screensaver or wallpaper, subscribe to a service such as online newsletters, or participate in online forums or communities. In exchange for Screensavers content or services the user may decide to pay a fee, download software, share personal information or view upfront advertising; it's up to the user. A variety of products and services are available at Screensavers, and Screensavers or any third party service provider used by Screensavers to provide such products and services may collect different types and levels of personal information for each model, product or service. 

## The Information We Collect 

The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

There are also times when you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card, or to refer them to our website or content (e.g., Tell-A-Friend). The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Mozilla Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

## How We Use the Information 

We, or a third party service provider used by Screensavers, may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. If you no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in the newsletter or communication or by emailing us at customerservice@screensavers.com. 

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your electronic greeting cards or referrals. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a review of a screensaver) we may publish your name and other information you have provided to us. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We also use one or more third parties to facilitate and optimize the services provided on Screensavers.com, and we may share personally identifiable information as necessary for such purposes. 

We sometimes use non-personally identifiable information to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. 

## Informed Consent 

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Screensavers.com will not disclose personally identifiable information to companies not owned by us who want to market products or services to you without your prior informed consent. 

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors 

Screensavers contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by websites that are not our own. 

From time to time Screensavers may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions or deals that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit. After such submissions, Screensavers.com has no control over third-party sponsors' use of this information. 

Screensavers will provide notice if third-party sponsors will so obtain such information. Screensavers.com may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information by such third parties or the methods by which third-parties collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). 

## Third-party Ad Serving 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to Screensavers.com in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Screensavers.com website, our third-party advertising companies may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

## Cookies 

To enhance your experience with our website, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our website. However, once you choose to furnish Screensavers with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings at Screensavers. For example, cookies may be used to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), and save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" may be used to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. Third parties (e.g., service providers) may also use cookies and web beacons on our website in connection with our website, products, and services.

## Our Commitment to Security 

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

## Special Note for Parents 

In an effort to be compliant with the Children's Online Protection Privacy Act (COPPA) it is our policy to collect no personally identifiable information from children. Therefore, all individuals are required to be 14 years and older to submit any personal information. 

## How to Contact Us 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Screensavers.com Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via email at the following address: 

Screensavers.com  
143 Varick Street  
New York, NY 10013  

Updated August 27, 2008
